[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":21465,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":22485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":30198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3934,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":34133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4438,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":38572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":934,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":39508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4830,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":44339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":932,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":45272,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":47439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1903,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":49343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If th e sum is  6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":52606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1025,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":53632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":55849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2 -0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":735,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":56585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2019,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":58605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1232,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":59838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perfo rm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1879,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":61718,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1006,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":62725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":" 5","response_history":[" 5"],"rt":2550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":65276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1207,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":66484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":[" ","1"],"rt":4691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":71175,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":721,"trial_type":" feedback ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":71897,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":[" ","0"],"rt":3902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":75801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0 because 3 + 3 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":651,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":76453,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller th an 6, th at's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":[" ","3"],"rt":3732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":80186,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 3 because 1 + 2 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":781,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":80968,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":83512,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 4 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 6 = 4.","rt":614,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":84126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":86401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0 because 4 + 2 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":86832,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub>  2? <br  /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":" ","response_history":[" "],"rt":1844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":88676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 2 because 0 + 2 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":670,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":89348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":[" ","2"],"rt":5597,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":94946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2 because 3 + 5 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":781,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":95728,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1875,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":97604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 because 1 + 4 = 5 and 5 is less t han 6.","rt":535,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":98140,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2009,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":100150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0 because 5 + 1 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":465,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":100616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to  it. If  the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1979,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":102595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 1 because 1 + 0 = 1 and 1 is less than 6.","rt":567,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":103162,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2140,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":105302,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 1 because 5 + 2 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":105734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":1327,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":107061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thin g that y ou combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":10950,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":118012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8649,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":126662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3177,"trial_type":"feedbac k","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":129840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2339,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":132180,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":641,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":132822,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3 ","response_history":[" ","3 "],"rt":3703,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":136526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1146,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":137673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2642,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":140315,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the ident ity unde r +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":882,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":141198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2875,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":144074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":680,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":144755,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the in verse of  4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"it's the negative/opposite if it is 6","response_history":["it's the negative/opposite if it is 6"],"rt":28557,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":173313,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":17084,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":190398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number usin g just 1 : 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":1698,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":192097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":8948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":201046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":3679,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":204726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3211,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":207938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</s ub> 5 +< sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1482,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":209421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":3884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":213306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1033,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":214340,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":217020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":816,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":217838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with it self rep eatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"it has to be able to make the number 6 with the other elements","response_history":["it has to be able to make the number 6 with the other elements"],"rt":15748,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":233586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":8943,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":242534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3411,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":245946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":2239,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":248186,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2564,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":250752,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2490,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":253242,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2144,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":255387,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":257452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":259652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please  explain  in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6140,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":265793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2215,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":268008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"it is just like 6, except it is 3 higher","response_history":["it is just likc","it is just like 4","it is just like 6, except it is 4 ","it is just like 6, except it is 4","it is just like 6, except it is 3 h igher"],"rt":13176,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":281184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":287919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":1522,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":289443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2120,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":291564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because you can add 7 to it get 9","response_history":["no, because","yes, because you can add 7 to it and get ","yes, because you can add 7 to it get 9"],"rt":15068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":306633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because you can add 6 to it and get 9","response_history":["yes, because you can add 6 to it and get 8","yes, because you can add 6 to it and get 9"],"rt":9111,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":315745,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.13-0 "},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because you can add 4 to it and get 9","response_history":["yes, because you can add 4 to it and get ","yes, because you can add 4 to it and get 9"],"rt":11837,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":327583,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because you can add 3 to it and get 9","response_history":["yes, because you can add 3 to it and get 98","yes, because you can add 3 to it and get 9"],"rt":8124,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":335708,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions ab out +<su b>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":47713,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":383422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","response_history":["n-1"],"rt":50612,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":434035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"the invese is going to be the number 'n'  minus wh atever the element is.","response_history":["the invese is going to be the number 'n' minus whatever the element is."],"rt":22804,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":456840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure.","response_history":["I'm sure there IS... bu","I'm sure there IS... b","Yes, it has to be ","YI","Y","I'm not sure."],"rt":93382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":550223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7348,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":557572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3959,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":89,"time_elapsed":561533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":5724,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":90,"time_elapsed":567257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in wo rds why  your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"because in order to be a generator, it needs to be able to divide evenly with a number 'n'","response_history":["because in order to be a generator, it needs to be able to divide evenly with a number 'n'"],"rt":29999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":91,"time_elapsed":597257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9075,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":92,"time_elapsed":606333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> a lways, s ometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Yes, because x should be divisible by x","response_history":["Yes, because x should be divisible by 2","Yes, because x should be divisible by 8","Yes, because x should be divisible by x"],"rt":142923,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":93,"time_elapsed":749257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":3835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":94,"time_elapsed":753094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background.  Please p ress \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1264,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":95,"time_elapsed":754359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","response_history":["32"],"rt":1893,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":96,"time_elapsed":756253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":97,"time_elapsed":758705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class y ou've co mpleted? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"college statistics","response_history":["statistics"," statistics","statistics","cstatistics","costatistics","colstatistics","collstatistics","collestatistics","collegestatistics","college statistics"],"rt":9701,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":98,"time_elapsed":768406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":99,"time_elapsed":774591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4038,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":100,"time_elapsed":778630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2561,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":101,"time_elapsed":781192,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":102,"time_elapsed":784434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":103,"time_elapsed":786319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1709,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":104,"time_elapsed":788029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":2865,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":105,"time_elapsed":790895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2535,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":106,"time_elapsed":793430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"interesting math concepts.","response_history":["nope!","intersting.  ","intersting. ","intersting.","intersting math concepts.","interesting math con cepts."],"rt":12237,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":107,"time_elapsed":805668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]